<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Treks Games</title>
    <link>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Treks Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 02:48:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://joshkomie.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Signal Defense</title>
      <link>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/SignalDefense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 02:48:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/SignalDefense/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ggj.s3.amazonaws.com/styles/feature_image__wide/games/screenshots/wave7.png?itok=tG7_VxVp&amp;amp;timestamp=1517375721&#34; alt=&#34;SignalDefense&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Tower Defense/RTS hybrid made for Global Game Jam 2018. Fend off waves of zombies by building towers, turrets and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;play-here-https-joshkomie-github-io-signal-defense:9e7a07dcc938de93003875d2e34bf0dc&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://joshkomie.github.io/signal_defense/&#34;&gt;Play Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pulsarcfirst</title>
      <link>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/pulsarcfirst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:12:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/pulsarcfirst/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve realized one of the reasons I develop games is to emulate that same sense of
excitement and adventure that you get from a great book or movie. Scripted gameplay in many ways,
is excellent at this. But it always nags at me because that kind of gameplay isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;lsquo;real&amp;rsquo;. I wanted to
create those same kind of exciting sequences, but between players - no scripting, quests or cutscenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are games that have done this before, which are usually thought of as sandbox mmos - Ultima online, SWG and EVE come to mind.
These games are inspiration for a game that I am developing tentatively called, Pulsarc. Pulsarc is a mmo (although It will be sometime, if ever, before the &amp;lsquo;massive&amp;rsquo; in mmo is achieved.)
Pulsarc will be focused on player-driven adventure and excitement. Here are some of the dreamed features for pulsarc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All structures player built and owned - Not only player housing, but player can build cities, shops, fortresses, jails, and more.
This will be achieved through a wide variety of placable objects, each having a function of some kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open pvp limited - This is a delicate subject. I think open pvp is a big part of the game - because danger creates excitement - just look at movies - the characters are often attacked or
come into dangerous situations, which creates excitement. On the flip side of the coin, it is important that the system is fair,
and prevents mismatched killing, trolling, and other negative behaviour. This will be one of the biggest design challenges of the game.
In the same category of pvp, features like thieving and jails are being considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than just combat - While combat will be part of the game, we want the game to be about more than just combat, with main other features being
crafting, building, gathering, exploring, city building and maintening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are the core ideas. Future blog will cover various elements of the game progress, including more design, as well as programming and implementation.
Heres a screen shot of the game in its current state.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oppose Inertia</title>
      <link>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/OpposeInertia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 02:48:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/OpposeInertia/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/tc7A3LK.png&#34; alt=&#34;OpposeInertia&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oppose Inertia is an in-development 2D space combat game focused on procedurally generated content. Explore star systems, each with unique enemies, which drop new weapons, abilities, or ship schematics for you to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;download-here-https-dl-dropboxusercontent-com-s-fjb902p7stihes5-opposeinertia-zip-dl-0:646f372f809063de700e6cfdc5ab68e1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/s/fjb902p7stihes5/opposeinertia.zip?dl=0&#34;&gt;Download Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Trader</title>
      <link>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/MonsterTrader/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 20:47:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joshkomie.github.io/post/MonsterTrader/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ludumdare.com/compo/wp-content/compo2//479518/22688-shot0-1440396805.png-eq-900-500.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34; title=&#34;Title&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most monsters make a living by terrorizing villages and eating adventurers.
You prefer to buy low, sell high, and make a nice profit. Don&amp;rsquo;t kill that wandering adventurer,
sell him an overpriced sword and send him on his way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Made in 48 hours for Ludem Dare 33.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://ludumdare.com/compo/ludum-dare-33/?action=preview&amp;amp;uid=22688&#34;&gt;Ludem Dare page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;amp;id=0BwGhngGtAvCtc1ZaNjB1cFZ2dFE&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>